[{"answer": "I -- I'm only trying to achieve one thing.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "But what are you trying to achieve with the cable news genre, if anything?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "It was interesting to do the speech, to work on the speech.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "When you said it, did you believe it yourself?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Well, first, let me just backup a little bit and say I don't have to live in the real world.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "If it's -- now you've had your toes dipped in our waters for a while, if you were running a news network, what would you do?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Well, I have no idea.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "Are Americans still the hardest working people on earth?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "You didn't write the speech though?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "But I mean for a president to be standing there today deliberately pandering like that to the Latino community at a Latino conference?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "No, no, of course you're not.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Am I being too cynical here?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Well, I liked it then because of the drug use.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "But what -- why do you like that solitude?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Have you arrived at a good place in your life now, do you think?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "I'm the luckiest guy in the world.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "The hard way, maybe, but you have?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "Every so often, I'm a single man.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Is this true?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "A million dollars a year.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "How much money?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "You get back $1 million a year?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Three million dollars.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "You paid $1 million to be able to fire me anytime you want?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "A great role, isn't it?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "She's a dream.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "What's Emily Mortimer like to work with?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Well, they've clearly had a fling before, right?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "-- base it on Keith Olbermann, I missed.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "-- mad as hell?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "To which the answer was?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "I actually think he's the new Spencer Tracy.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Yes, you know?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Listening is a bit part of it.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "What is the art of great acting, other than listening?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "You know, Meryl.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "And, Jeff, when you look around now in the firmament of great actors, who, for you, stands out, male or female, right now as pound for pound a great actor?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "That Jim Carey buggered off.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "What have you heard?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Yeah, starting to creep back to where it was before.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Starting to do well?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "10:00 p.m.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Time?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "You should -- you're definitely allowed to call me Todd.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Am I allowed to call you Todd?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Well, you know, my first reaction was -- it was horrifying, you know.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "When you heard what has happened, what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Yes, I knew Whitney.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Did you know Whitney well?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "You know, I -- I was thinking about it and it was the only way that I felt -- I would feel comfortable proceeding with the show and celebrating all of these other musicians, because it was about trying to find that fine balance between celebrating her legacy, giving love to this wonderful, amazing entertainer, and, at the same time, respecting all of these young artists and all of these established artists who were either nominated for Grammys or performing on the show and not putting them in the position where they have to perform at a memorial.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "What gave you that idea to do that?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Of course I do.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Do you understand the particular pressure, as a former -- that led her to enter that spiral of self-abuse towards the end?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Well -- well, yes, you drift away.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "Was music always your first love?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "Whatever goal I'm going -- I want to achieve, achieving it", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 763, "question": "What is it to you?", "qSentId": 762}, {"answer": "I'm not saying it's going to happen imminently.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 771, "question": "Oh, God, I don't even want to think about that, right?", "qSentId": 770}, {"answer": "Well, you're doing a hell of a lot.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 796, "question": "But, you know, things -- all being relative and everything being even, it's what you don't do that you'll ultimately regret, you know?", "qSentId": 795}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 798, "question": "My Connect Studio is available now?", "qSentId": 797}, {"answer": "You know what, I'm working on it.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 814, "question": "When is the new album out?", "qSentId": 813}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120708pmt", "aSentId": 864, "question": "Will you please, please marry me?", "qSentId": 863}]